vuze.com 2017-12-15

# Vuze - Privacy

## Vuze Platform Privacy Notice

Welcome to the Azureus Software, Inc. ("Vuze") applications, platform, web site (www.vuze.com), and any other web sites, applications, or services operated or produced by Vuze (collectively, the "Vuze Platform"). Vuze values the privacy of the users, subscribers, publishers, members, and others who visit and use the Vuze Platform (collectively or individually, "You" or "Users").

By using the Vuze Platform, you expressly consent to the information handling practices described in this notice.

This Privacy Notice is incorporated into and is subject to the Vuze Platform Terms of Service. Your use of the Vuze Platform and any personal information you provide through the Vuze Platform are subject at all time to this Privacy Notice and the Terms of Service.

### TABLE OF CONTENTS

  1. The Information Vuze Collects
  2. The Way Vuze Uses Information
  3. (Additional)Information About Cookies, Web Beacons, Pixels
  4. When Vuze Discloses Information
  5. Your Choices
  6. Data Security
  7. Children's Privacy
  8. International Visitors
  9. In the Event of Merger or Sale
  10. Changes and Updates to this Privacy Notice
  11. Effective Date, Date Last Modified
  12. Vuze Contact Information

### 1\. The Information Vuze Collects:

User-provided Information: You may provide to Vuze what is generally called "personally identifiable" information (such as your name, email address, postal mailing address, home/mobile telephone number, credit card number and billing information) if you upload, purchase, or download certain content or products from the Vuze Platform, enter contests or sweepstakes, or otherwise use the features and functionality of the Vuze Platform.

"Cookies" Information: When you access the Vuze Platform, we may send one or more cookies - small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer. Vuze may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie disappears after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Vuze Platform. Persistent cookies can be removed. Please review your web browser "Help" file to learn the proper way to modify your cookie settings.

"Automatically Collected" Information: When you access the Vuze Platform or open one of our HTML emails, we may automatically record certain information from your system by using different types of tracking technology. This "automatically collected" information may include Internet Protocol address ("IP Address"), a unique device or user ID, version of software installed, system type, the content and pages that you access on the Vuze Platform, and the dates and times that you visit the Vuze Platform.

### 2\. The Way Vuze Uses Information:

Vuze uses the information that you provide or that we collect to operate, maintain, enhance, and provide all of the features and services found on the Vuze Platform as well as to track user-generated content and Users to the extent necessary to comply as a service provider with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act.

We will use your email address, without further consent, for administrative communications such as notifying you of major Vuze Platform updates, for customer service purposes, to address copyright infringement or defamation issues, or to contact you regarding any content that you have posted to or downloaded from the Vuze Platform.

Vuze uses all of the information that we collect to understand the usage trends and preferences of our Users, to improve the way the Vuze Platform works and looks, and to create new features and functionality.

Vuze may use "Automatically Collected" information and "Cookies" information to: (a) automatically update the Vuze application on your system; (b) remember your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you access the Vuze Platform; (c) monitor aggregate site usage metrics such as total number of visitors and pages accessed; and (d) track your entries, submissions, and status in any promotions or other activities.

### 3\. (Additional)Information About Cookies, Web Beacons, Pixels:

Like most sites, We, our analytics providers, and/or our content and ad providers may set or access cookies, web beacons & pixels on your computer (including "mobile" device). We may use such, including those for Google Analytics, to obtain information about your visits to &/or uses of our sites (sometimes referred to as a Platform, and including re-direct sites) and our offerings (including offer windows or pages that may open, including when you choose to start a download &/or installation process, and which may include interstitials or offers for Programs, services, &/or products not mentioned when you choose to learn more about or initiate a download of an offer, Program, product, or service), and other sites. We consider the interstitials/offer windows to be a page that is part of our site or Platform and covered by this Privacy Policy, unless indicated otherwise in connection with an interstitial/offer. Cookies, beacons & pixels help us, Google, partners, and ad networks understand how our visitors (you) engage with our or their properties, sites, pages, or Platforms, and other sites. They may collect information and report usage data without personally identifying you to Google, such as how often you visit this site (and other sites) and open or proceed with offers, what pages you visit when you do so, and what other sites you visited or used prior to and after coming to this and other sites (including offer windows/pages). We use the information we get from Google Analytics and our cookies, beacons & pixels to improve our sites, Platforms, offerings, and attempt to serve you more relevant ads. Although Google Analytics or we may place a cookie on your web browser or device to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this site, or our other sites, or Platforms, the Google Analytics cookie cannot be used directly by anyone but Google, which allows us to access analytical information regarding our sites or Platforms. Google Analytics has its own [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) and [currently available opt-outs](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). You can stop cookies by disabling or removing them, however, this might log you out of websites or change website behavior. As is the case with most websites, simply visiting the website may be your consent to the automatic placing of cookies, pixels, and/or web beacons on your device, which you may clear by clearing your browser of cookies, history, etc. (Please consult the guide for your browser on how to do this.) You may read [here](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/) how Google uses data when you visit or use our or partners' sites (including offer windows or pages) and apps,. More information about what may be collected, used, and stored by Us or Google may be found elsewhere within this Privacy Policy (or Privacy Statement) as well as on Google's sites (including [here](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/technologies/types/) & [here](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage#gajs)). Google Analytics can also be used, together with some of the advertising cookies (which may be described elsewhere), to help show more relevant ads on Google properties (like Google Search) and across the web. 

### 4\. When Vuze Discloses Information:

Vuze does not share your personally identifiable information with other organizations for their marketing or promotional uses without your express consent. Please be aware, however, that any personally identifiable information that you voluntarily choose to display on the Vuze Platform - such as when you publish video credits or profile information - becomes publicly available and may be collected and used by others without restriction.

We may disclose User information to affiliated companies or other businesses or persons to: provide web site hosting, maintenance, and security services; fulfill orders; conduct data analysis and create reports; offer certain functionality; and assist Vuze in improving the Vuze Platform and creating new services features. We require that these parties process such information in compliance with this Privacy Notice, we authorize only a limited use of such information, and we require these parties to use reasonable confidentiality measures.

Vuze may disclose User information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright law) or respond to a court order, judicial or other government subpoena, or warrant. In some cases, we may make such disclosures without providing notice to Users.

Vuze also reserves the right to disclose User information that we believe, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to take precautions against liability; protect Vuze from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses; to investigate and defend ourselves against third-party claims or allegations; to assist government enforcement agencies; to protect the security or integrity of the Vuze Platform; or to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Vuze, our Users, or others.

### 5\. Your Choices:

You may, of course, decline to share your personally-identifiable information with Vuze, in which case Vuze will not be able to provide to you some of the features and functionality found on the Vuze Platform. You may update, correct, or delete your user information and preferences at any time by following the directions here.

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you account access or making corrections to your information. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times.

### 6\. Our Commitment to Data Security:

Vuze uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Vuze, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, Vuze makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

If Vuze learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. Vuze may post a notice on the Vuze Platform if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach you should notify us through our online web form or by mail.

### 7\. Our Commitment to Children's Privacy:

If you are under 18 years of age, then please do not use or access the Vuze Platform at any time or in any manner.

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Vuze does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information from persons under 18 years-of-age. If Vuze learns that personally-identifiable information of persons less than 18-years-of-age has been collected on or through the Vuze Platform, then Vuze will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

If you are the parent or legal guardian of a child under 18 who has become Vuze Platform member, then please contact Vuze through our online web form or by mail to have that child's account terminated and information deleted.

The following are some resources that may help parents and legal guardians in monitoring and limiting your childrens' access to certain types of material on the Internet. While Vuze does not endorse these products, we provide information about them as a public service to our community.

### 8\. International Visitors:

For Users visiting the Vuze Platform from the European Economic Area or other non-U.S. territories, please note that any data you enter into the Vuze Platform will be transferred outside the European Economic Area or such other non-U.S. territory for use by Vuze and its affiliates for any of the purposes described herein. In addition, because Vuze operates globally, we may make information we gather available to worldwide business units and affiliates. By providing any data on the Vuze Platform, you hereby expressly consent to such transfers of your data to the United States or other countries.

### 9\. In the Event of Merger or Sale:

In the event that Vuze is acquired by or merged with a third-party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information that we have collected from Users as part of that merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control.

### 10\. Changes and Updates to this Privacy Notice:

This Privacy Notice may be revised periodically without further notice to you and this will be reflected by a "last modified" date below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, we only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Notice in effect when we received that personal information. Your continued use of the Vuze Platform constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Notice and any future revisions.

For revisions to this Privacy Notice that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of personal information you have provided to us, we will make reasonable efforts to notify you and obtain your consent before implementing revisions with respect to such information.

### 11\. Effective Date, Date Last Modified:

Privacy Notice effective as of December 13, 2006.

Revised May 11th, 2016, by including clarifying information about Google Analytics, cookies, web beacons, pixels. Effective immediately.

### 12\. Vuze Contact Information:

Please contact Vuze with any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice, your personal information, and our third-party disclosure practices or your consent choices through our online web form or by mail at: 774 Mays Blvd., #10-568, Incline Village, NV 89451. We will respond to your inquiry as promptly as possible.
